It's cute.
かわいいですね
So
そ
I'm a little bored.
こ ちょっと退屈割りしてみて
There's something erotic in it.
なんかエロいの入ってるね
Move your butt forward.
お尻もっと前にして
Shift it to yourself
それ自分にずらしてみ
hand.
て
You have a naughty one.
エ ッチなの持ってるね
Kuro-chan, please open this.
クロちゃん開いてあげてこれ
Kuro-chan, come sit next to me.
クロちゃんこれ、隣に座ってごらん
Samura-chan.
サムラちゃん
yes.
はい
Yeah.
うん
Will you make me feel good at the end?
最後 にチンチン気持ちよくしてくれる?
It's already grown.
もう大きくなっちゃった
Pero from below.
下からぺろい
Fill the tip with blood.
先っぽに血をいっぱいして
Erotic way of licking.
エロい舐め方を
I'll smoke some more and watch it now.
もっといっぱい吸って今見とく
copper?
どう?
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
It's ticking.
カチカチな
Yeah.
うん
black
クロ
Chan: Today is the best date.
ちゃん 最強のデートだな、今日は
Looks like it's spit.
ツバだらしい
The people are big.
人大きいね
Maybe Kuro-chan.
クロちゃんかも
Repeat flat.
フラットしこしこ繰り返して
Kuro-chan, this might be it.
クロちゃんこれかも
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
Samura-chan, does your mouth feel good?
サムラちゃん、口気持ちいい?
Don't take it out yet.
まだ抜いちゃダメだよ
Accept it all.
全部受け止めて
Let's get it all out.
全部出しちゃおうじゃん
I'll take a look.
見してみせーし
Get the electricity out.
電気出して
This is the last time I've seen Sakura-chan.
これで桜ちゃん見収めです